我要走了
Well, I'm off.
我很喜欢我们周六
While I do love our tradition
依旧要聚在一起吃感恩节剩菜的传统
of still getting together on Saturday for thanksgiving leftovers,
也许下次我们可以买一只
maybe next time we can order a turkey
没有视界[黑洞边界]的火鸡
that doesn't have its own event horizon.
谁在乎
Oh, well, who cares?
反正要是在我的天体物理俱乐部里
I know it's totally gonna slay them
大家肯定都会笑死的[爱上的]
in my astrophysics club.
有人爱上那种俱乐部的成员才怪呢
First time anyone in that club gets slayed.
让我跟你拥抱道别吧
Let me give you a hug goodbye.
难以相信你居然已经上大学了
I cannot believe that you're already going to college.
感觉昨天你还只是个学习大学课程的
It seems like yesterday when you were a little girl
小姑娘而已
reading at college level.
瞧瞧啊
Check you out!
谢谢
Thanks.
我有个超性感的自习搭档要过来 所以...
I have a hot study partner coming over, so --
你在做什么呀 我的小厨子
What are you making, my little chef?
我在做利大意面
I'm making pasghetti!
你真可爱
You are adorable.
我还记得当年我用"利大意面"这种三脚猫招数
I remember when I had everyone in the palm of my hand
博取所有大人欢心的风采
with a two-foot putt like "Pasghetti."
咱俩都清楚你知道这个词怎么说
We both know you know how to say it.
两位 再次感谢你们帮我收拾那栋待售房
Hey, guys, thanks again for helping me to get that listing.
西里尔的房子
Cyril's house.
-很性感吧 -必须呀
- Pretty sexy, huh? - Ridonk.
那地方让花花公子豪宅
This place makes the playboy mansion
像个老头子的家一样
look like an old folks' home.
现在好像是的
Which I guess it kind of is now.
超大泳池 超赞视野
Infinity pool, killer views,
最高端的游戏厅 家庭影院
state-of-the-art game room, home theater...
再加上那个四人淋浴
Plus that four-person shower.
你知道西里尔就是在那里认识他的新丈夫的吗
Did you know that's where Cyril met his new husband?
连安全码都很性感
Even the security code's sexy.
真的 按键上写着"性感"
Literally. It spells out "Sexy" on the keypad.
连我都觉得那有点太拼了吧
Even I think that's trying too hard,
我一般最多用用香体喷雾
and at this point, I'm mostly body spray.
单是那个超大浴缸就在四个饶舌视频中出现过
And that master bathtub alone has been in four rap videos
还有《日界线》特别节目的一个谋杀重演出现过
plus a murder re-creation on a "Dateline" special
剧集名叫《按摩到死》
called "Rub-a-dub Dead."
我小的时候
When I was younger,
我爸是房地产中介的事情
I was a little embarrassed
让我有点小尴尬
my dad was just a real-estate agent.
但我长大了一点之后 我意识到
But as I got older, I realized,
他的工作可能不是世界上最酷的
Hey, he may not have the coolest job in the world,
但是他养活了我们
But he puts food on the table
而且他还坐拥很多空房子
and has access to a bunch of empty houses
让我能偷偷溜进去
I can sneak into."
希尔格罗夫三居室带的游泳池好赞啊
Wow. Nice pool at the three-bedroom in Hillgrove.
瞧啊
Well, looky here,
终于有个孩子对咱们的家庭产业有兴趣了
one of my kids showing interest in the family biz.
不知道我够不够聪明来干这活
Oh, I don't know if I'm smart enough for that.
得背这么多东西
You have to remember so much stuff,
比如什么人什么时候看房
like when anyone's gonna be there.
日程表就是用来做这个的
That's what the datebook's for.
而且你还得记住
Plus you have to remember
那么些组合密码
all of those lock-box combinations.
我用的都是一个非常特别的生日
I just use a very special birthday.
胡迪尼的生日
Houdini's.
我的手表落在了西里尔的浴缸边上
I left my watch by Cyril's tub.
我一向格外谨慎 不会在老爸的这些房子
I'm usually extra careful not to leave any trace
留下我去过的痕迹
that I was at one of my dad's houses,
但是这个浴缸有16个脉冲射流
But this tub has 16 pulsating jets,
整个缸底都震动着
and the whole floor vibrates
给人进行瑞典爽身按摩
with something called "Swedish Release".
爽得我花了20分钟才找到我的车
It took me 20 minutes to find my car in the driveway.
我很抱歉 外公
I'm so sorry, grandpa.
我得去工作了
I have to go do this thing for work.
-谢谢 -等等
- Thanks. - Hold on.
每个人走之前都要拿一袋肉
No one leaves this house without a bag of meat.
再见 亲爱的
Bye, honey.
你能相信我们的小姑娘现在
Can you believe how conscientious
这么认真工作吗
our little girl has become?
周六还赶去上班
Racing off to work on a Saturday.
当然有30%的可能是因为她以为今天是周五
There's a 30% chance she thinks it's friday,
但还是很认真啦
But still.
你还在生我气吗
Are you still mad at me?
我昨天冲菲尔发脾气了
I lost my cool on Phil last night.
但我要解释一下 我昨天奔波了一天
But in my defense, I had been traveling all day,
结果我们对
and we had different ideas
如何度过夜晚产生了分歧
about how we were gonna spend the evening.
快点进来
Get in here right now.
快到浴缸里来 你这坏姑娘
Get in this tub, you dirty girl.
亲爱的 你太贴心了
Oh, honey, that is so sweet,
但我今早5点就起床一直忙到现在
but I've been up since 5:00 a.m.
别想太多 宝贝 快跳进来吧
Don't overthink it, babe. Just take the plunge.
太好了 你回来了
Oh, good, you're back.
你能把水下摄像机拿过来吗
Could you grab the underwater camera?
你在跟它们一起洗吗
You're bathing with them now?
它们跑到了车库 浑身是油
They waddled into the garage and got oil on them.
后来它们自己过来的时候
And then when they were in here by themselves,
就是想在这里胡闹 所以...
all they wanted to do was horse around, so...
我今早跑去伯克利
I spent the morning in Berkeley
下午去波特兰
and the afternoon in Portland.
我有权洗个澡干净清爽一下
I deserve to feel clean again.
但现在这个舒适放松
But now the nice, soothing tub
我幻想了一整天的浴缸
that I've been dreaming about all day
到处都是羽毛 机油还很有可能有禽流感
is filled with feathers and motor oil and probably bird flu.
所以算了 你坐好了
So, no. No. You just sit tight,
我去用后院里的水管
and I will use the hose in the backyard.
那你还能把摄像机拿过来吗
Could you still grab the camera?
好吧 我是凶了点
Okay. I was harsh.
但从波特兰回来的航班真的太辛苦了
But the flight back from Portland was rough.
我头顶的隔板上放着折叠自行车
The overheads were packed with foldable bikes,
我还跟一个用打字机的家伙坐在一起
and I was sitting next to a guy using a typewriter.
不过 菲尔就是不肯原谅我
Still, Phil is really holding on to this one.
菲尔在生我的气
Well, Phil's mad at me.
过来 小姑娘
Come here, little girl.
我来抱抱你
Let me give you a hug.
你今儿个可真舍得自己的拥抱啊
You're not shy with those hugs today, are you?
-过来吧 -还有我吗
- Oh, and come here. - Oh, me too?
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what it is,
不过一到节日我的情绪就容易激动
But I get so emotional around the holidays.
天哪
Oh, God.
不 不 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
邓菲先生 是你吗
Mr. Dunphy? Is that you?
海莉
Haley?
安迪 你来这里干什么
Andy, wh-- uh, what are you doing here?
布置一下明天的参观日
Setting up for an open house tomorrow.
你来这里干...
What are you d--
我滴个水神啊 谁用了浴缸
Splish, splash, who was taking a bath?!
我
Me.
我昨晚偷偷溜进来 但是水龙头漏水
I snuck over last night, but the faucet leaked,
我猜我是太过放松了
and I guess I was so mellowed out
我忘了把水放干
I forgot to drain the tub.
你这放松得真彻底啊
That's pretty darn mellowed out.
你还熏香了吗
Were you burning incense?
是啊 当然了
Uh, yep. Sure was. Okay.
我去铺几条毛巾 你把浴缸放干
Well, I'll lay some towels down. You drain the tub.
堵住了吗
Is it stuck?
没有 我在倒影里看我的妆花了没
No, I'm checking my makeup in the reflection.
当然是堵住了啊
Yes, it's stuck.
来吧 我来帮你
Here. Let me help.
不用不用 我可以的
No, no. I can get it.
来吧 好了
Here. Okay.
天哪
Oh, my god.
放松 我没事
Relax, I'm okay.
不 这不是李尔·韦恩视频里的浴缸吗
No. Isn't this the tub from the Lil Wayne video?
我把我们的衣服放进烘干机了
I put our clothes in the dryer.
我做了个行政决策
I made an executive decision --
选了爱尔兰山干燥片
Went with the Irish mountain dryer sheets.
爱尔兰山闻起来是什么样的
What does an Irish mountain smell like?
30到35分钟后就知道了[模仿爱尔兰口音]
We'll find out in 30, 35 minutes.
别告诉我爸我来过好吗
Hey, uh, don't tell my dad I was here, okay?
这种小忙应该没问题[模仿爱尔兰口音]
I suppose I could do you that wee favor.
能再帮我一个忙吗
Do me a second favor...
我也不喜欢这个口音
Yeah, I don't love it, either.
你为什么要
Hey, why were you
来这里泡澡呢
taking a bath over here, anyway?
我只是想要一点私人时间
Oh, I just wanted a few hours to myself.
我住在父母家的地下室里
You know, I live in my parents' basement,
跟迪兰分手了
I broke up with Dylan,
还因为感恩节吃得太多心情抑郁
I was depressed about how much I ate at Thanksgiving...
你跟迪兰分手了啊
You broke up with Dylan, huh?
是啊 实际上就是在
Yeah. Actually, it was the day
我们在电影院看到你和贝丝那天
that we saw you and Beth at that movie.
你们在一起的感觉特别好
You guys seemed so great together
我当时就想着 我也想要那样
I guess I just thought, "I want that."
我挺幸运的
I am pretty lucky.
不过坦白讲
But for what it's worth,
贝丝和我并不完美
Beth and I are not perfect.
筹划婚礼的时候问题就暴露出来了
Things come up when you plan a wedding.
真的有种叫"摩门教剧"的东西吗
Really? There's such a thing as Mormon drama?
贝丝的叔叔发现我们在接待处
There was when Beth's uncle found out
为客人供应咖啡之后就有了
we're serving coffee at the reception.
另外 她不想让我办单身派对
Plus, she doesn't want me to have a bachelor party.
完全不行吗
At all?
这是你余生之前的最后一晚
It is one night before the rest of your life.
-你应该办的 -我也是这么说的
- You should do it up. - That's what I said.
对着镜子里的自己说的 不过你说得对
Well, to my mirror, but you're right.
我应该在安稳下来之前来一场冒险
I deserve one adventure before I settle down.
你瞧你做了什么 在这
Look what you did. Here.
你确实该做点有趣的事
Well, yeah, I mean, you got to do something fun.
要不你试试看调好它
Um... maybe you try and fix it.
好吧 应该很简单
Yeah. It should be simple enough.
好吧 我说的不是这个意思
O...kay... I did not mean to do that.
要不试一下这个
Um, maybe try this one?
我们最好别再乱按按键了
Maybe we shouldn't touch any more buttons.
是啊
Right.
我们刚说到什么来着
Uh... what were we talking about?
新的冒险
Having an adventure.
天哪 是我爸吗
Oh, God, is that my dad?
这下糟糕了
'tis a fine kettle of fish we're in!
进洗衣间
Get in the laundry room!
动物园传来坏消息
and sad news from the zoo,
熊猫春发患上了...
Chuffa the panda has suffered a m--
不要乱碰
Stop touching stuff!
你今儿个可真舍得自己的拥抱啊
Well, you're not shy with those hugs today, are you?
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what it is,
不过一到节日我的情绪就容易激动
but I get so emotional around the holidays.
-我知道了 -我说真的
- Oh, I get it. - I really do.
-我爱你 -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
所以说今年
So, this year,
我们要用迈阿密之行给全家一个惊喜
we're surprising the family with a trip to Miami.
旅游公司需要所有人的驾照
The travel company needs everybody's driver's license
好订机票
to book the flight.
这就是为什么我们需要
That's where "sticky fingers" here
这位"妙手空空"了
comes in handy.
所有人都有一个坏表亲
Everybody has a bad cousin
教会你一些事
that teaches you a few things.
比如怎么抽烟 怎么偷东西
Like how to smoke, how to pick-pocket,
没有钥匙怎么启动车
how to hot-wire a car,
怎样通过在鞋子里放大头针
how to put tacks on your shoe
改变测谎试验的结果
when you want to throw off a-a lie-detector test.
这是哪一个表亲
Which cousin was this?
我就是那个表亲
I am the cousin.
再见
Bye.
菲尔 还记得我们一年前
Phil, honey, remember those gutter covers
订的水槽盖吗
that we ordered like a year ago?
好消息
Good news.
他们终于发货了
They shipped!
真棒
That's exciting.
如果我哪天为水槽盖激动你一定要杀了我
Please kill me if I ever find gutter covers exciting.
我知道 婚姻变得比名模聚会上
I know. That marriage is staler
那一盒纸杯蛋糕还要无味
than a box of cupcakes at a supermodel retreat.
菲尔
Oh, hay, Phil!
再次感谢你能来
Thank you again for coming!
我们的荣幸 你一直都这么
It was our pleasure. You're always so...
慷慨地款待我们
generous to have us!
抱歉 我没想挠你痒
Ay, I'm sorry. I didn't wanted to tickle you.
只不过我很喜欢这种布料的感觉
It's just that I love how this fabric feel.
这种材料叫什么名字
What is the name of this material?
牛仔裤料
Uh...jeans.
它们摸起来还特别紧
Oh, and they feel so tight, huh?
节日专用窍门
Oh, a little holiday trick.
能让我少吃点
Keeps me from eating too much.
你太紧张了
I think you're too tense.
到底发生了什么...
What the hell is going --
-亲爱的 -什么事
- Hey, hon. - Yeah?
我们今天还没有什么机会聊天
We didn't get much of a chance to talk today.
你好吗
How are you?
不怎么好
Not great.
实话说 我不想烦你
But, honestly, I don't want to bore you.
那你至少说给我听听
Oh, well, at least start the story.
好吧 我从波特兰回来时
Okay. Um, well, I got back from Portland,
菲尔和鸭子们一同泡在浴缸里
and Phil was in the bathtub with all the ducks,
我完全爆发了
and I just completely lost it.
是的 我道过歉了
And, yes, I've apologized...
可他这次完全不肯原谅我
but he's really not letting go of it this time.
你真有力气
I -- you're so strong!
工作占去了你大部分时间 对吧
Work's taking up a lot of your time, isn't it?
你这次站在他那边吗
You're taking his side on this?
我跟你是一样的
I've been you on this.
我在工作上遇到麻烦的时候
When I was bogged down with work,
经常跟你妈吵架
your mother and I fought all the time.
也许不是因为鸭子 我没那么奇怪
I mean, maybe not about ducks. I'm not a weirdo.
但也许他生气是因为你不在身边
But maybe he's mad at you because you're not around.
可我只出了两次差
But I only took like two trips.
也许你人在心不在
Just 'cause you're around doesn't mean you're around.
老妈就喜欢说这种绕来绕去的话
That's one of those loopy things mom would say.
我以前也假装听不懂
I used to pretend that I didn't understand it, too,
但我其实懂的
but I did.
为什么不多花点时间陪陪彼此
Why not just make some time for each other?
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
也许我应该找个周末带他到外面玩玩
Maybe I'll take him for a weekend up north, huh?
-你怎么看 -挺好的
- What do you think? - Sure.
或者抛弃他
Yeah. Or leave him.
你还是挺有魅力的 我觉得挺好
You're still attractive. Worked great for me.
我还在感叹
I am still in shock about
那些冰块模子怎么能这么便宜
the deal we got on those ice-cube trays.
对啊 感觉像是不要钱随便拿
I know. It's like we pulled off the great tray robbery.
上面说我们可以直接
You know, it says we're supposed to
丢进洗碗机
throw them in the dishwasher,
但我还是打算手洗
but I'm just gonna give them a rinse.
你真是太坏了
Oh, you are so bad!
既然我们该做的都做完了
You know, since we got all of our errands done early
现在两个人都有时间
and we do have a little extra time on our hands...
莉莉又去朋友家睡了
and Lily's at a sleepover.
就是那里 往右边一点
Just -- right there. A little to the right.
好了 非常棒 放手
Right -- yeah. Perfect. Now turn.
我想给床垫翻个儿想好久了
I have been wanting to flip that mattress for months.
就是啊 把事情做完的感觉真好
I know. It feels good to get stuff done.
-是啊 -真好
- Yeah, it does! - Yes!
除了莉莉
So, other than Lily,
我们也没有什么活着的理由了吧
we have no real reason to be alive, right?
天哪 是我爸吗
Oh, God, is that my dad?
去洗衣间
Get in the laundry room!
动物园传来坏消息
And sad news from the zoo,
熊猫春发患上了...
Chuffa the panda has suffered a m--
别乱碰
Stop touching stuff!
你确定我们能这么做吗
Are you sure we should be doing this?
米奇尔 我们刚刚为了翻床垫而击掌庆祝
Mitchell, we just high-fived over flipping a mattress.
那比菲尔和克莱尔为水槽盖激动可悲多了
That's way sadder than Phil and Claire's gutter covers.
再说了 西里尔不会在意的
Plus, Cyril won't care.
他在我们家玩得不是挺开心的吗
It's not like he hasn't had his fun in our place.
-啥 什么时候 -在你生日派对上
- What? When? - At your birthday party.
他和格雷戈里在浴室里待了一个小时
He and Gregory were in the bathroom for like an hour.
别想歪 那是因为格雷戈里的隐形眼镜掉了
Oh, no. That's 'cause Gregory lost a contact lens.
好吧 你呆得太可爱了
Okay, you're adorable.
好了 我现在要去调点鸡尾酒
All right, now, I'm gonna go make some cocktails,
然后等到太阳下山
and then when that sun goes down...
我们就到热水浴缸里放松放松 怎么样
you and I can get cozy in the hot tub, okay?
好像很赞
Ohh, I like the sound of that.
我放点有情调的音乐 好吗
I'm gonna put on some mood music, huh?
小卡 他们这儿没有能控制整间房的
Hey, Cam, don't they have a remote
-遥控器吗 -有的吧
- that controls everything? - Yeah, I think so.
你知道他放在哪儿吗
You know where he keeps that?
反正我们俩的经常陷在沙发缝里
Well, ours is always getting buried in the couch.
找到了
Oh, here it is.
我爱这首歌
Ooh, I like this song.
你想看我伴舞一曲吗
Would you like a show to go with it?
-米奇尔 -那是谁
- Mitchell! - Who's Mitchell?
我是魔力米奇
I'm Magic Mitch.
白天我是焊接工人
Welder by day...
业余时间我是脱衣舞男
stripper by choice.
我未婚的姐姐怀着七个月的身子
My unwed sister is seven months pregnant.
我母亲得了妇科病
My mother has some uterine issues
医保却不给报销
not covered by medicare.
如果你愿意慷慨解囊 我会献上...
But if you want to make it rain, I will --
米奇尔 亲爱的 你没事吧
Mitchell! Sweetie, are you okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
灯呢 没坏吧 还能亮吗
How's the lamp? Is it okay? Does it work?
-好着呢 你看 -那就好
- It's fine. See? - Okay.
好了 来吧 做正经事要紧
All right, now, come on. Let's get back on track.
-是的 -我这就去调酒
- Yes. - I'll go get the cocktails.
你请随意
You make yourself comfortable.
必须的
I sure will.
换首欢快点的歌
Maybe something a little more lively?
这又不是《亚当和史蒂夫》 该死的
It's not "Adam and Steve", damn it.
极目所见 尸体遍野
Corpses as far as the eye can see.
你若不了解你家的冰块模子
What you don't know about your ice-cube tray
也许会害死你
could kill you.
也许是第一个
Maybe the first station.
什么情况
Oh, what's happening?
我的天
Geez.
别担心克莱尔会怎么样了
Don't worry about Claire.
我整个下午[的时间]都是你的
You've got me all afternoon.
亲爱的 你还记得一年前
Honey, remember those gutter covers
我们订的那批水槽盖吗
that we ordered like a year ago?
好消息 他们终于发货了
Good news. They shipped!
真棒
That's exciting.
克莱尔最近工作都很忙
Claire's been working a lot lately,
这样真是挺棒的
and it's been...great.
这样我多出很多时间打《格尔斗兽》
It's given me a lot more time for "Battle Beasts of Gar",
一款大型的角色扮演网游
this massive online role-playing game.
而且自从用了西里尔的顶尖游戏系统
And with Cyril's state-of-the-art gaming system,
我就能把我那半矮人半公牛的火法师
I've been able to take my half-dwarf, half-ox fire mage --
喷火小牦牛[脑残]
PyroMiniYak --
刷到更高的级别
to a whole new level.
第三级
Level three!
我们那个阵营 暴徒战队
Our guild, thugsquad,
一直在策划突袭我们的死敌阵营
has been trying to plan a raid against our arch-rival guild,
他们的头儿是残忍的性感小兽
led by the ruthless SexyBeast,
然后我收到通知 我们终于要发动突袭
and I got a text saying it was finally happening.
但前提是我必须得搞定克莱尔
That is, if I could get Claire
让她容我消失几个小时
to be okay with me disappearing for a few hours.
菲尔 亲爱的 我想跟你道个歉
Phil, honey, I want to apologize.
为啥要道歉 你又没有
For what? You haven't -
露过面 没错
been around at all. I know.
的确如此 所以我想补偿你
I know, and I want to make it up to you.
我挺伤心的
It was very hurtful.
肯定的 只是我有时候真的工作太忙了
Yeah. It's just sometimes I get so caught up in work
所以就算我出现在这里 也是心不在焉
that even when I am around, I'm not around.
说得真好
So well put.
完全无法反驳
I don't want to beat you up about that.
其实我的心情有好转
It's healing time now.
我想下午去西里尔家
You know, what I'd love
待个几小时
is a few hours at cyril's house this afternoon.
要我陪你一起去吗
With me?
其实吧
Actually...
我是想去玩
I was thinking about that
我喜欢的那个角色扮演游戏
role-playing thing I'm into?
我和菲尔时不时会
Phil and I have, on occasion,
玩几次角色扮演来为我们的婚姻增添情调
adopted various alter-egos to spice up our marriage.
西里尔家听上去确实
Cyril's house does sound
适合做点浪漫的事
kind of perfect for some romance.
而且菲尔愿意翻篇我也挺高兴的 那就...
And I like that Phil wants to move past this, so...
你有给今天下午的游戏
Did you have a particular genre in mind
想好什么主题风格吗
for this afternoon's game?
有 中世纪幻想
Yes. Medieval fantasy.
很好
Great.
非常感谢
Thank you.
性感小兽 等着被打屁屁吧
Oh, SexyBeast, you are gonna get so spanked.
冰箱
Refrigerator.
不对 应该是"箱冰"
No, say "Fridger-frater."
但那就是冰箱
But it's refrigerator.
集中点注意力 小屁孩
I need you to focus, kid.
那是"箱冰" 我们放"三门治"的地方
Fridger-frater -- where we keep the sammiches.
大家好像都很喜欢乔 随便了
People seem delighted by Joe. Whatever.
但是我那位很漂亮的自习搭档要来我家
But I had that fetching study partner coming over,
然后我发现可以利用乔的呆萌
and I realized I could use Joe's by-the-numbers cuteness
来助我施展多情的魅力
to my amorous advantage.
就连我都觉得这话太"曼尼特色"了
Even for me, that was a lot of Manny.
但是那叫三明治
But it's sandwich.
你到底有没有在听
It's like you're not even trying.
好了 应该是她到了
Okay, that's probably her.
你就表现得可爱一点好吗 给我点面子
L-look, just be cute, okay? For my sake.
就和男生用小狗狗吸引女生一样
It's like when guys use puppies to attract girls.
-你好 曼尼 -奥莉薇 请进
- Hi, Manny. - Uh, Olive. Please come in.
那是我弟弟 乔
That's my little brother, Joe.
别介意他的那些小锅小碗
Don't mind his little pot there.
你的锅里有啥来着
Hey, what do you have in there again?
有意大利面吗
Some kind of pasta dish?
你是小狗狗吗
Are you a doggie?
是的 他经常做这些萌萌的动作
Yeah, he's always doing adorable stuff like that
因为他很崇拜我
'cause I'm his hero.
真有爱
I love that.
你是好狗狗还是坏狗狗呢
Are you a good doggie or a bad doggie?
好可怕噢
Oh, scary!
-好可爱 -对啊
- Adorable. - I know.
那个 我们开始学习吧
Uh, so should we head up?
我的天 把他拉开
Oh, my god! Get it off me!
不 乔 快下来乔
Uh...no! Joe! Joe!
乔 松手
Joe, let go!
-你在干嘛 -他在咬我 快帮帮我
- What are you doing? - He's biting me! Do something!
不能这样 坏蛋乔
No! Bad Joe!
-小坏蛋 -你这样他咬得更凶
- Bad Joe! - That's just making him bite me harder!
别把人当成"三门治" 乔
A person is not a sammich, Joe!
乔 你在干嘛
Joe, what are you doing?
乔 放手
Joe, let go!
你知道菲尔会来这儿吗
Did you know Phil was gonna be here?
不知道 我在泳池都要穿T恤
No. I-I wear a T-shirt in the pool.
你觉得我会想让他看到我们现在这样吗
Do you think I want him to see me in the middle of this?
走 走
Go. Go.
我们只有一箱六罐装的啤酒
Well, we only have one six-pack.
所以其实那些女孩不来是好事
So, in a way, it's good all the girls said no.
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
那个 我的高考备考小组
Oh, um, my S.A.T. prep group
需要找个安静的地方学习
needed a quiet place to study.
你们学的又不是表演
You ain't studying acting.
行了 我们没空
Okay. We don't have time for this.
-你爸 -- -所有人都不许动
- Your father -- - Everybody freeze!
跆拳道
Taekwondo!
盯紧那些血蝙蝠 速度烧光它们
Eyes on those blood bats! Let's burn 'em down fast!
疯技87 拜托给点力
Come on, Madskillz87!
你要干扰他们施放魔咒
You're supposed to be on spell interrupt!
别再让那些术士躲过寒霜陷阱了
Do not let those casters get off any more frost traps!
丽萨 看来岩浆恶魔这能靠你跟我对付了
Lisa, looks like it's you and me on the lava demon.
挺住
Hang tight!
药粉
Powder!
为了疯技 迅速把他们遣回地狱去
Let's send them back to hell in time for Madskillz
别误了他的双簧管课
to make it to his oboe lesson!
-我之前还觉得我爸让我丢脸了 -闭嘴
- And I thought my dad was embarrassing. - Shut up.
好了 我们走
Okay, let's go. Let's go.
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
Is anybody here?
放下[武器]
Drop it!
直奔主题啊
Ohh, gettin' right to it.
我喜欢
I like it.
求你了 先生 发发慈悲[模仿英国口音]
Please, sir, have pity.
我真的只是个普通的小贼
It's true I'm just a common thief,
但如果你肯大发慈悲
but if you have mercy,
-我会好好补偿你的 -是的
- I'll make it worth your while -- - Oh, yes.
这个中世纪的生物是什么
What medieval creature is this?
半人类半机器的电焊工吗
Half-man, half-robot... welder?
如果你现在出来 你这个满脸假笑的懦夫
If you come out now, you simpering coward,
也许我会对你发点慈悲的
maybe I'll show you a little mercy.
请别伤害我 都是她的主意
Please don't hurt me! It was her idea!
我本不想进展这么快的
I'm the one who wanted to go slow!
-罗本 -艾丽克斯
- Reuben? - Oh, Alex!
-克莱尔 -怎么又是罗本
- Claire? - Reuben again?
高中开学第一天他披着蝙蝠侠披风
He wore a batman cape to the first day of high school!
你真的想现在指责我的选择吗
You're really judging me right now
你穿得就像漫画大会上的妓女
when you look like a hooker at comic-con?
是的 我在理解上出了些问题
Yes, this was a miscalculation on my part,
-我这就去拿我的外套 -克莱尔
- and I will be getting my coat... - Claire,
-怎么回事 -尽快离开这里 我...
- what is going on? - ...and getting out of here as soon as I -
卢克
Luke?
你后面藏的是啤酒吗
Is that beer behind your back?
快出来 你被禁足了
Get out here! You are so grounded!
邓菲夫人 你当家教吗
Mrs. Dunphy, do you ever tutor?
老兄
Dude!
我把我的滑板车一拿就赶紧撤了
I'm just gonna grab my razor scooter and bounce.
-生日快... -生日快...
- Happy birth-- - Happy birth--
得了 你们知道今天谁也不过生日
No, you know it's no one's birthday.
你们来这的原因估计跟那二位一样
You're probably here for the same reason as those two.
严格来讲 这是你们的错
Well, technically, this is your fault,
因为我们担心我们的婚姻
because we were afraid our marriage
会像你们的一样越来越沉闷
was getting as boring as yours.
不过从她的着装来看
Though based on her outfit,
我们得再努把力了
we need to work a little harder.
你们都应该为自己的行为感到惭愧
You should all be ashamed of yourselves.
我才是唯一一个有权到这来的人
I'm the only one authorized to be here.
你们偷偷潜入 既不尊重我
By sneaking in, you've disrespected me,
也破坏了客户对我的信任
and violated the trust between me, my clients,
更亵渎了这所风情万种的房子
and this sexy, sexy house.
不 不
No. No!
好极了 丽萨死了
Great. Now Lisa's dead.
我要你们马上离开这里
I want everybody out of here right now!
至少我们还有自己的房子
Well, at least we have our house to ourselves still.
魔力米奇还有别的招式吗
Does magic Mitch have another set him in?
当然 没两下子怎么买他奶奶的术后特制鞋
Yeah. His grandma's built-up shoe isn't gonna pay for itself.
好吧 你的风骚姿势还得练练
Okay, we need to work on your sexy patter.
快下来吧
Off the lamp. Off the lamp.
好吧 以免你产生什么愚蠢的想法
Okay, before you get any stupid ideas,
我告诉你 罗本和我到这来
Reuben and I broke in here
是为了帮他补习数学
so I could help him with his math.
给那家伙补习可真是辛苦你了
Good luck getting through to that guy.
他笨得要死
He's clueless.
-亲爱的 -什么事
- Honey. - Yes?
对不起 刚才我情绪那么激动
I'm sorry. That -- that little outburst
主要是针对他们的
was mainly directed at them.
不管是什么误会让你这样
Whatever misunderstanding led to this,
我都很开心
I'm... happy about.
我以为你不开心
I thought you were upset
是因为我们最近很少有时间在一起
because we hadn't spent any time together.
而你又说想要玩角色扮演...
And then you said you wanted some role-playing fun...
真的吗
Really?
亲爱的 我知道你最近工作很辛苦
Honey, I know you've been working really hard lately,
我很珍惜我们在一起的时光
and I-I appreciate any time I can get with you.
-所以你没生我的气吗 -安静 埃尔文的妓女
- So you're not mad at me? - Silence, Elvin harlot.
对不起 大人
Ohh, sorry, my lord.
小女子无意冒犯
Didn't mean to offend.
但我生气了 懦弱的姑娘
But you have, craven wench.
而我将要惩罚你...
And I shall mete out punishment as --
我能听见你们在偷笑
I can hear you guys giggling.
起码我还有女朋友
At least I have a girlfriend!
都走了
All clear.
刚才真是惊悚
Well, that was crazy.
自从叠杯决赛后
My ticker hasn't gotten a workout that good
我的心脏就再没经受过这么大的考验
since I made the finals of that cup-stacking competition.
我是不是该把浴袍拿到楼上去
Hey, should I take these robes upstairs?
我把我的这件拿回去洗吧
I'm gonna pop mine in the washer.
上面大概能有三磅的冷汗了
I've got about three pounds of tension sweat in here.
我...
I, uh...
之前的事我觉得有些抱歉
I feel kind of bad about before.
不必 我们也没做什么
Don't. We didn't do anything.
我知道 只是我觉得如果...
I know. It just felt like something could've...
-如果他们没... -是啊
- If everybody hadn't... - Yeah.
你知道是什么原因吗
You know what it is.
-都怪这房子 -都怪这房子
- It's the house. - It's the house!
那壁炉 还有音乐...
I mean, the fireplace, the music...
抽风的沙发床
The crazy couch-bed.
任何人都会性奋起来的
Anyone could've gotten swept up.
-任何人 -任何人 是啊
- Anyone. - Anyone. Yeah.
我该走了
Well, I should get going.
是啊 没错
Yeah. Totally.
不管怎么样 这个下午过得很愉快
I mean, it was a fun afternoon, though.
结婚前我一直想来一次疯狂的冒险
I wanted one crazy adventure before I got married,
而我得到了
and I got one.
那就好 的确很愉快
Good. It was fun.
回见
I'll see you later.
好的
Yep.
乔在斯黛拉的笼子里干什么
What's Joe doing in Stella's cage?
他清楚自己做了什么坏事
He knows what he did.
出来 孩子 出来
Go on, boy! Get!
杰
Jay!
我在想
So, I was thinking,
既然迈阿密离哥伦比亚只有几小时的路程
since Miami's only a few hours away from Colombia,
为什么不让我的亲戚飞到迈阿密去
why don't we have my relatives fly to Miami
这样所有人就都能在一起了
so that the whole family can be together?
歌洛莉亚 我爱你的家人 真的
Gloria, I love your family. I do.
-可是 -你总是这样
- But -- - This is so typical.
为你的家人我们可以做任何事
We do everything for your family,
但轮到我的家人时 你就...
but when it comes to my side of the family, then --
-我们不去迈阿密了 -什么
- We're not going to Miami. - What?
我为所有人买了去哥伦比亚的机票
I bought everybody plane tickets to Colombia.
杰
Ay, Jay!
你不应该这样做的
That's not what you were supposed to do!
我想你的意思是"你不必这样做的"
I think you mean "You shouldn't have,"
也许你是对的
and you're probably right.
不 我的意思是你不该这么善解人意的
No! I mean you shouldn't have been nice about this at all!
你应该说
You were supposed to say,
"为什么不能换个时间见你的家人呢"
"Why can't we see your family some other time?"
而我会说 "什么时候"
and I would say, "Like when?"
而你会说 "有什么好选的"
and then you would say, "Is never an option?"
而我会说 "怎么能这样说话 杰·普里契特"
and I would say, "That's so mean, Jay Pritchett!"
然后你会说
and then you would say,
"就没什么能补偿你的方法吗 歌洛莉亚"
"Is there a way that I can make it up to you, Gloria?"
然后我会说 "不如..."
and then I would say, "How about if..."
不如什么
If what?
不是吧
Oh, no.
你们好啊
Hola! Hola! Hola!
好啊 快进来
Yeah. Come in, come in.
你觉得会是短暂小住还是长期驻扎
Does this feel like a short visit to you or a long one?
怀孕的那个把婴儿车都带上了 你觉得呢
The pregnant one brought a stroller.